const questions = [
    {
        question:'Who was Nigeriaâ€™s first prime minister?',
        option_a:'Obafemi Awolowo',
        option_b:'General Aguiyi Ironsi',
        option_c:'Abubakar Tafawa Balewa',
        option_d:'Shehu Shagari',
        answer:'Abubakar Tafawa Balewa'
    },
    {
        question:'Who is the first Nigerian president?',
        option_a:'Obafemi Awolowo',
        option_b:'Dr Nnamdi Azikiwe',
        option_c:'Abubakar Tafawa Balewa',
        option_d:'Shehu Shagari',
        answer:'Dr Nnamdi Azikiwe'
    },
    {
        question:'How many ministers do we have in Nigeria?',
        option_a:'34',
        option_b:'38',
        option_c:'43',
        option_d:'36',
        answer:'43'
    },
    {
        question:'The first general election in Nigeria was held in',
        option_a:'1957',
        option_b:'1960',
        option_c:'1959',
        option_d:'1958',
        answer:'1959'
    },    
    {
        question:'Who was the first Nigerian to become a Nobel Laureate?',
        option_a:'Obafemi Awolowo',
        option_b:'Wole Soyinka',
        option_c:'Ngozi Iweala',
        option_d:'Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie',
        answer:'Wole Soyinka'
    },
    {
        question:'Which country won the 2018 World Cup?',
        option_a:'Brazil',
        option_b:'France',
        option_c:'Argentina',
        option_d:'Italy',
        answer:'France'
    },
    {
        question:'When did Nigeria become a republic?',
        option_a:'1959',
        option_b:'1960',
        option_c:'1999',
        option_d:'1963',
        answer:'1963'
    },
    {
        question:'How many Local Governments do we have in Nigeria?',
        option_a:'750',
        option_b:'774',
        option_c:'776',
        option_d:'763',
        answer:'774'
    },
    {
        question:'What is the centenary?',
        option_a:'150',
        option_b:'100',
        option_c:'90',
        option_d:'99',
        answer:'100'
    },   
    {
        question:'When was Nigeria formed?',
        option_a:'1959',
        option_b:'1915',
        option_c:'1916',
        option_d:'1914',
        answer:'1914'
    },
    {
        question:'Who gave Nigeria her name?',
        option_a:'Micheal Taiwo Akinkunmi',
        option_b:'Dr Nnamdi Azikwe',
        option_c:'Flora Shaw',
        option_d:'General Aguiyi Ironsi',
        answer:'Flora Shaw'
    },
]